<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Fruit</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_1">Apple</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_2">Avocado</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_3">Banana</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_4">Blueberry</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_5">Cacao</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_6">Cherry</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_7">Coconut</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_8">Cranberry</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_9">Durian</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_10">Fig</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_11">Grape</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_12">Guava</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_13">Kiwi</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_14">Lemon</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_15">Lime</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_16">Longan</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_17">Mango</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_18">Melon</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_19">Orange</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_20">Papaya</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_21">Passionfruit</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_22">Peach</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_23">Pear</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_24">Persimmon</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_25">Plum</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_26">Raspberry</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_27">Strawberry</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_28">Tamarind</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_29">Tomato</string>
    <string name="fruit_name_30">Watermelon</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_1">An apple is an edible fruit produced by an apple tree (Malus domestica). Apple trees are cultivated worldwide and are the most widely grown species in the genus Malus.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_2">The avocado (Persea americana) is a medium-sized, evergreen tree in the laurel family (Lauraceae). It is native to the Americas and was first domesticated by Mesoamerican tribes more than 5,000 years ago.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_3">A banana is an elongated, edible fruit - botanically a berry. produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_4">Blueberries are a widely distributed and widespread group of perennial flowering plants with blue or purple berries. They are classified in the section Cyanococcus within the genus Vaccinium.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_5">Cacao is the dried and fully fermented seed of Theobroma cacao, from which cocoa solids (a mixture of nonfat substances) and cocoa butter (the fat) can be extracted.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_6">A cherry is the fruit of many plants of the genus Prunus, and is a fleshy drupe (stone fruit).</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_7">The coconut tree provides food, fuel, cosmetics, folk medicine and building materials, among many other uses.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_8">Cranberries are a group of evergreen dwarf shrubs or trailing vines in the subgenus Oxycoccus of the genus Vaccinium.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_9">Durian is the edible fruit of several tree species belonging to the genus Durio. There are 30 recognised Durio species, at least nine of which produce edible fruit.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_10">The fig is the edible fruit of Ficus carica, a species of small tree in the flowering plant family Moraceae.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_11">A grape is a fruit, botanically a berry, of the deciduous woody vines of the flowering plant genus Vitis.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_12">is a common tropical fruit cultivated in many tropical and subtropical regions.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_13">Kiwi is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_14">The lemon (Citrus limon) is a species of small evergreen trees in the flowering plant family Rutaceae, native to Asia, primarily Northeast India (Assam), Northern Myanmar or China.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_15">Lime is a citrus fruit, which is typically round, green in color, 3–6 centimetres (1.2–2.4 in) in diameter, and contains acidic juice vesicles.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_16">Longan is a tropical tree species that produces edible fruit. It is one of the better-known tropical members of the soapberry family Sapindaceae, to which the lychee and rambutan also belong.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_17">Mango is an edible stone fruit produced by the tropical tree Mangifera indica</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_18">Melon is any of various plants of the family Cucurbitaceae with sweet, edible, and fleshy fruit. The word "melon" can refer to either the plant or specifically to the fruit.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_19">Orange is a fruit of various citrus species in the family Rutaceae, it primarily refers to Citrus × sinensis, which is also called sweet orange, to distinguish it from the related Citrus × aurantium, referred to as bitter orange.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_20">Papaya is the plant species Carica papaya, one of the 21 accepted species in the genus Carica of the family Caricaceae.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_21">The passion fruit is so called because it is one of the many species of passion flower, the English translation of the Latin genus name, Passiflora, and may be spelled "passion fruit", "passionfruit", or "passion-fruit".</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_22">The peach (Prunus persica) is a deciduous tree first domesticated and cultivated in Zhejiang province of Eastern China.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_23">Pears are fruits produced and consumed around the world, growing on a tree and harvested in the Northern Hemisphere in late summer into October.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_24">Persimmon  is the edible fruit of a number of species of trees in the genus Diospyros.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_25">A plum is a fruit of some species in Prunus subg. Prunus. Dried plums are called prunes.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_26">The raspberry is the edible fruit of a multitude of plant species in the genus Rubus of the rose family, most of which are in the subgenus Idaeobatus.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_27">The garden strawberry or simply strawberry is a widely grown hybrid species of the genus Fragaria, collectively known as the strawberries, which are cultivated worldwide for their fruit.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_28">Tamarind is a leguminous tree bearing edible fruit that is probably indigenous to tropical Africa.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_29">The tomato is the edible berry of the plant Solanum lycopersicum, commonly known as the tomato plant.</string>
    <string name="fruit_desc_30">Watermelon is a flowering plant species of the Cucurbitaceae family and the name of its edible fruit.</string>
    <string name="day">Day %d</string>
</resources>